<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="//assets/xslt/rss.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="//assets/css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>IPÊ Analytics</title>
		<description>IPÊ Analytics, transformando dados brutos de monitoramento para gerar informações valiosas ao gerenciamento da rede.</description>
		<link>http://localhost:4000//</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Characterizing Brazil’s Connectivity</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//measurement/open-announce-brazil-study/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;The peering ecosystem of Brazil (IX.br) has his own characteristics when analyzed in perspective to regions like the United States and Europe. The IX.br has become worldwide the largest national set of public Internet eXchange Points (IXP) and shows a growing number of internationally connected Autonomous Systems (AS). Despite its considerable success, we have little understanding of its deployments and performance. Motivated by recent developments in connectivity to the country and the growing commercial interest from Internet Service Providers (ISPs) and Application Providers (App Providers) to interconnect, we profile Brazil’s network starting from the IXPs going towards ASs level information. Through extensive measurements, we reveal Brazil’s footprint, its traffic patterns, volumes, external connections, and the treatment given to international traffic going to and from the country. This study is a fundamental part of our project Networks@Scale which includes IXPs, ISPs, app providers and the end-users, exposing the dynamic aspects and evolution of Internet online service delivery chain ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//measurement/open-announce-brazil-study/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>INF/UFRGS sends two students to the CoNEXT 2016 Conference</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//conferences/conext2016-presentation/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;INF/UFRGS researchers Oliveira R. and Marcos, P. will present two new papers at the Student
Workshop of the ACM Conference on emerging Networking EXperiments and Technologies (CoNEXT) at Irvine, CA, USA.
ACM CoNEXT is one of the top conferences in networking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//conferences/conext2016-presentation/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Coverage Analysis at IXPs in Brazil</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//measurement/ixforum-cgi-presentation/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
				<description></description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//measurement/ixforum-cgi-presentation/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
